insidesales.com 2007-12-14

# On-Demand Lead Management, Dialer, and CRM Solutions - InsideSales.com ™

Privacy Policy Overview        Safe Harbor       Terms of Use

**Sales Team Automation, LLC - Privacy Policy**  
  
At Sales Team Automation, we are committed to protecting your privacy as described below. This Privacy Policy ("Policy") discloses the privacy practices for the Sales Team Automation website, located at [www.SalesTeamAutomation.com](http://www.salesteamautomation.com/).

Except as otherwise discussed in this Policy, this document only addresses the collection, use, and disclosure of information that we (i.e., Sales Team Automation and its agents) collect from you on this site. Other sites that are not owned or controlled by Sales Team Automation may have their own privacy policies that apply to those sites. In addition, certain third-party offerings that are made via the Sales Team Automation website are subject to the terms of third-party privacy policies and the terms of this Policy shall not apply. We encourage you to ask questions, to review the privacy policies of other sites, and to be very cautious before you disclose your personally identifiable information to other sites. 

For a fuller discussion of our privacy practices, please see the Frequently Asked Questions ("FAQ") below. This Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of our Terms of Use Agreement and is subject to modification at any time without your prior consent. You are responsible for reviewing the Policy each time before using our website or providing any personal information. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please contact us via e-mail at [company@SalesTeamAutomation.com](mailto:company@salesteamautomation.com). If you believe we have violated the Policy, please notify us, and we will promptly investigate and try to remedy the problem. 

Listing and Links to Frequently Asked Questions 

1\. What information do we collect from you?  
2\. Where do we collect information from you?  
3\. How do we use the personal information we collect from you?   
4\. Who is collecting information?   
5\. With whom do we share your information?   
6\. What are my choices regarding collection, use, and distribution of my information?   
7\. How can I update, correct, or delete my personally identifiable information?  
8\. What security precautions are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of my information?   
9\. What about the privacy of visitors who are 13 and under?   
10\. What are cookies and how do they collect, use, and distribute information?   
11\. Where can I find any changes to the Privacy Policy?   
**  
Frequently Asked Questions  
**  
**1\. What information do we collect from you?**  
We collect information via the website that falls into one of two categories: personally identifiable information and aggregated information. Personally identifiable information is information that is actually used to identify you. We collect personally identifiable information whenever you voluntarily submit it to the website, including your name, e-mail, company, mailing address, title, area of expertise, telephone number, and credit card information, plus your preferences regarding Sales Team Automation products (collectively, "personally identifiable information").  
Aggregated information is information that is not directly tied to a specific user, such as the number of people who visit the website from various states. We collect and store statistics and other information about the online activities of our visitors on an aggregated (i.e., collective) basis. For example, we track the number of people who view each page, the order in which pages are viewed, and other information to learn which features are the most popular and to refine our design and marketing efforts. Aggregated information also includes information that indirectly (i.e., combined with information collected about you off the website) could be used to identify you, but in practice is not  
back to FAQ

**2\. Where do we collect information from you?**  
Sales Team Automation gathers information in the following ways: 

_Software Downloads_ : When you download any of our free software from our website, we may collect and use certain personally identifiable information (e.g., the software you selected, your planned use for the software) for use by Sales Team Automation.

_View a Video_ : When you view a video, we may keep a record of what videos were viewed for use by Sales Team Automation.

_Purchases_ : When you make a purchase, we keep track of what you bought, along with other personal and product information (such as payment, shipping, and warranty data).

_Newsletters & Promotional E-mails_: From time to time, we may offer free electronic newsletters and promotional e-mails as a service to our registered users, based on a voluntary subscription. If you sign up, we will send you newsletters and e-mails periodically listing industry news, industry events, product information, and other promotions. You will only receive a newsletter if you have requested it during registration or directly from our signup form. To stop receiving our newsletter, send an e-mail to us at [company@SalesTeamAutomation.com](mailto:company@salesteamautomation.com).

_Webmaster Lists_ : If you are a webmaster and send us an e-mail, we will collect your e-mail address.

_Chat Rooms and Bulletin Boards_ : From time to time, we may make chat rooms and bulletin boards available to registered users. Please remember that postings to bulletin boards and chat rooms become public information; thus, you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personally identifiable information within such forums, as it may be collected and used by third parties.

_Search Terms:_ From time to time, we may offer the ability for you to search our website for information that interests you. We may save those search terms and display certain banner ads tied to your search term.

_Online Surveys and Polling_ : If you participate in an online survey or interactive poll, we may ask you for your e-mail address and your preferences in order to track voting.

_EEE-Postcards_ : From time to time, we may offer you the ability to send an e-postcard, or e-mail, to your friends containing content or links to our site or to content that you think your friends would find interesting. In order to do this, we must collect the user names and e-mail addresses of your friends.

_Contact Information & Third-Party Data_: If you contact Sales Team Automation by e-mail or letter, we may keep a record of your personal correspondence. Thus, if you report a problem with our website, we may collect such information in a file specific to you. Moreover, if you contact us through our feedback area, we require your name and e-mail address in order to send you a reply. Additionally, if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on our site, we may keep the information in a file specific to you.

_Browsing_ : An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the web, allowing web servers and ad servers to identify your computer. Sales Team Automation collects IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to gather broad demographic information, to enable ads to be served on our site, to report aggregated information to our advertisers, for security purposes, and to monitor the level of activity on our site.

_Cookies_ : Cookies are small data text files that are sent from a computer serving our web pages or ads to your computer during a browsing session. The cookies are typically stored on your computer's hard drive and are used by websites to simulate a continuous connection to that site. To learn more about our use of cookies, click here.

_Clear GIFs_ : Clear GIFs, which are sometimes called "web bugs," are invisible graphic images embedded in one or more web pages on this site. Sales Team Automation (and in the future, its banner ad servers) use clear GIFs to get a better idea of the types of users who visit our site and their personal preferences. When you access a page with a clear GIF, a message is sent to our server, the server of one of our banner ad servers, or the server of a consultant who does data analysis for Sales Team Automation. The message identifies the IP address of the computer that fetched the clear GIF, the URL of the page where the clear GIF is located, the URL of the clear GIF, the date and time the clear GIF was received, the type of browser that fetched the clear GIF, and a previously set cookie value.

_Banner Advertisements_ : In the future, we may include banner advertisements on our website. If you click upon a banner advertisement displayed on our website, you will leave our website (unless, of course, the banner is to another page of our website). In cases where clicking on a banner takes you to a third-party site, if you later disclose personally identifiable information on that site, the third party may be able to tie that information to the banner ads and pages you were viewing on our website.  
back to FAQ

3\. How do we use the personal information we collect from you?  
Operation of the Website and E-mail: The aggregated and personally identifiable information we collect from you is used to operate and enhance our website. We collect personally identifiable information in order to learn more about you so we can provide you with content, products, and advertising that you are more likely to find interesting. Sales Team Automation also uses registered user information to contact users when necessary and to send promotional e-mails.   
Tracking Website Pages Viewed: Demographic and profile data is also collected via our website. We monitor the actions of visitors to our website to determine what our users find interesting. Sales Team Automation does research on our users' and visitors' demographics, interests, and behavior based on the information provided to us during browsing, upon registration, during a promotion, from our server log files, or from surveys. We will use this data to tailor the visitor's experience on our website, to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze website usage patterns, to improve our content and product offerings, and to customize our website's content, layout, and services.

Advertisements: From time to time, we may display advertisements. Aggregated information is used to sell and deliver advertising. We may disclose aggregated information about our website to third parties, including informing our advertisers whether their advertisement was effective. By knowing a little about you, we will be able to deliver more relevant advertisements and content to you in the form of targeted banners, industry event and news services, and e-mail promotions. For example, advertisers may give us an advertisement and tell us the type of audience they want to reach (e.g., computer programmers with expertise in Java™ applications). We could then take the advertisement and display it to users and visitors who meet those criteria. In this process, the advertiser will not have direct access to individual account information; only we have access to individuals' accounts. We may share this aggregated data with advertisers, but we will only develop summary reports (not about individuals) for our advertisers.   
Agents: We also may share your personally identifiable information with third parties for the purposes of providing services to our website or to Sales Team Automation itself.  
Merchants: Except as disclosed in this Policy, we will not share personally identifiable information about our users with other merchants and third parties without your permission.  
E-mailings: We will send registered users e-mail containing information we think they will find interesting, such as information about news, new products and services from our selected partners. It is our policy not to send messages to members who have asked us not to do so. By using our website, you expressly agree to receive this information. If you do not wish to receive these communications, you have the ability to opt out. Please see the "What are my choices regarding collection, use, and distribution of my information?" section below.  
Cookies: Our website and third-party ad servers use cookies for marketing purposes in order to make sure you do not see the same ads repeatedly and to track in the aggregate the pages on our site visited by our users. We also use a shopping cart cookie to keep track of items you selected until you check out or delete the items. To learn more about our use of cookies, click here. Clear GIFs: Our website and third-party ad servers use clear GIFs for marketing purposes in order to make sure you do not see the same ads repeatedly and to track in the aggregate the pages of our site visited by our users, as well as the types of users visiting those pages.  
back to FAQ

4\. Who is collecting information?   
Co-branded Services: When you are on the Sales Team Automation website and are asked for personally identifiable information, you are sharing that information with us alone, unless it is specifically stated otherwise or as discussed in this Policy. However, some website services are offered in conjunction with a partner company. In order to provide a co-branded service to you, it is necessary for us to share your personally identifiable information with our partner company. If you do not want your data to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer by not using our service.  
Promotions, Contests, and Sweepstakes: Promotions that run on the website may be sponsored by Sales Team Automation and another company. Some or all data collected during a promotion may be shared with the sponsor. If data will be shared, you will be notified prior to the time of data collection or transfer (for example, in the terms and conditions of a contest). You can decide not to participate in the promotion if you do not want your data to be shared.   
Links and Banner Ads to Third-Party Sites: Please be aware that sites on our website may contain links to other sites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third parties. The information practices of those websites linked to our website are not covered by this Policy. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. Additionally, other companies or ad servers that place advertising on our website may collect information about you through the use of cookies or clear GIFs when you view or click on their advertising. We cannot control this collection of information. You should contact advertisers directly if you have any questions about their use of the information they collect.  
Ad Servers: From time to time, we may use third-party advertising services to serve banner advertisements on our website. In order to ensure you do not see the same advertisement repeatedly, for any page on which we display banner ads, they may place a cookie on your computer's hard drive. Your computer will receive these cookies, which contain a unique but anonymous tracking number, unless you set your browser to refuse them. They will collect information from visitors to our site regarding the URLs from which they came; their IP addresses; domain types (e.g., .com); browser type; operating system; the country, state, and telephone area code where their servers are located; the products and pages of our site that visitors viewed during their visit; time and date particular ads were served; and banner ads clicked upon. To learn more about the information our ad server collects, click here link to no. 10  
Framing/Windows to Third-Party Sites: In addition to providing links to other websites, we sometimes window third-party sites for your convenience. If you click to learn more information, a window or frame containing the third party's site may appear. Any time you are in a window (unless the window is another part of the Sales Team Automation website), you should assume your personal information is being collected, used, and disclosed in accordance with the windowed site's policies.  
Chat Rooms and Bulletin Boards: Except as otherwise expressly discussed in this Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. If you participate in chat rooms or message boards, your user name will be displayed with your comment or posting. Information you provide while using services such as website chat rooms and bulletin boards is available for all to see; discretion should be used in disclosing personally identifiable information within such forums, as it may be collected by third parties. We encourage you to ask questions and to be very cautious before you disclose your personally identifiable information to others.  
Surveys and Polling: From time to time, we may use a third party to conduct surveys about our website or polls about a particular issue. If we do, we will either tell you in advance who that third party is, or obtain their promise that personally identifiable information will not be used or further shared with anyone outside of Sales Team Automation.  
back to FAQ

5\. With whom do we share your information?   
Merchants: Other than as disclosed in this Policy or with your permission, we will not share your personally identifiable information with merchants. If you do give permission to share your information, you should know that once your personally identifiable information is shared with third parties, we cannot control how it is used or who else it may be shared with.  
Fulfillment: Some online activities necessarily lead to disclosure of your personally identifiable information to third parties, such as when you include your name and e-mail address in an e-mail to a third party or when you order merchandise in the shopping areas of our website for direct shipment to you. For example, in order to fulfill certain product orders, we must share your information with the product manufacturer, payment processor (e.g., credit card companies), and shippers.  
Data Analysis Agents: The information collected through the website may be provided to an outside company for the purpose of analysis. This analysis is to help us to improve our sites and services to you, and to notify you of special offers that may be of interest to you.  
Chat Profile, Chat Rooms, and Bulletin Boards: It is important to note that information you provide as part of your chat profile is not confidential and is accessible by the public. Similarly, any information you provide in chat rooms, message boards, or other public forums is not confidential. For such activities, a separate warning may not be provided. Your choice to disclose personally identifiable information in these cases is voluntary.  
Ad servers and Advertisers: Our ad servers will have permission to use their cookies' identification numbers to serve ads on our site and to collect aggregated information to create statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to third-party advertisers. However, these statistics will not include personally identifying information.  
Compliance with Service of Process or Law Enforcement: Although it is unlikely, we may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide personally identifiable information to the appropriate governmental authorities. If we receive such a request, without prior notice to you we will disclose personally identifiable information upon receipt of a court order subpoena, to investigate hacking attempts, or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation. If we receive a subpoena as part of third-party civil litigation, we will attempt to provide you with electronic notice (i.e., via e-mail) fourteen (14) days prior to disclosure of personally identifiable information. Moreover, we may release account information without notice to you when we in good faith believe such release is reasonably necessary to enforce or apply our Terms of Service Agreement or to protect the rights, property, computer security, and safety of our website, our users, or others.  
Sale of the Company: You agree that we may assign, sell, license, or otherwise transfer to a third party your name, address, e-mail address, member name, and any other personally identifiable information collected by us via the website in connection with an assignment, sale, joint venture, or other transfer or disposition of a portion or all of the assets or stock of Sales Team Automation or its affiliated entities.  
back to FAQ

6\. What are my choices regarding collection, use, and distribution of my information?   
E-mail and Promotional Mailings: We may from time to time send you e-mail or other communications regarding our products and services. If you do not wish to receive these promotional mailings, the website provides users the opportunity to opt out of receiving these communications by sending an e-mail to [company@SalesTeamAutomation.com](mailto:company@salesteamautomation.com). After that, Sales Team Automation users will not receive future communications or mailings.  
Cookies: If you are uncomfortable with the idea of cookies, we recommend disabling cookie support in your browser. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits; however, if you do, you may not be able to use certain services or take advantage of the personalized features of our website. Additionally, it is possible that some areas of the website will not function properly if you set your browser to refuse cookies. You will need cookies for customizable areas of the site, such as message boards and chat rooms. To learn more about our use of cookies, click here.  
back to FAQ

7\. How can I update, correct, or delete my personally identifiable information?  
Website Services: Sales Team Automation provides you with a limited ability to access and edit the personally identifiable information you have provided to us. Following registration you can review, change, or delete the information you have submitted. We encourage you to update your information promptly if it changes. To change, modify, or delete the information you previously provided, visit the registration page on our site or send an e-mail to [company@SalesTeamAutomation.com](mailto:company@salesteamautomation.com).

Chat and Bulletin Board Postings: You cannot change or remove any public postings made on our bulletin boards.

E-mailing and Newsletters: The website also gives users options for removing their information from our database so they will not receive future communications or receive our service any longer. Users can send an e-mail to [company@SalesTeamAutomation.com](mailto:company@salesteamautomation.com).

Reviews/Correct/Update: We provide users the ability to reviewing and modify information previously provided by the creation of a new user profile and deletion (unsubscribe) of the incorrect profile.   
No Comprehensive Deletions: We will retain in our files information you have requested to remove if that information is necessary to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, or enforce our Terms of Service Agreement. Except as noted, upon request we will delete your information from our databases. However, due to the fact that we "back up" the data stored on our systems, such prior information is never completely removed from our databases. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personally identifiable information will be completely removed from our backed-up databases in response to your requests.  
back to FAQ

8\. What security precautions are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of my information?   
You can be assured that your personal and account information is reasonably secure on our website. We employ encryption technology in all parts of our website that require you to provide your financial or credit card information. The personally identifiable information we collect is stored in secure operating environments that are not available to the public. Credit card information is encrypted. All the information we collect and store is protected by our firewall. Also, any information we store at our business is kept physically secure, and only designated employees may obtain access to it. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet.  
While we strive to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems.  
We cannot fully ensure that your private communications and other personally identifiable information will not be inadvertently disclosed to third parties. We may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. If we need to investigate or resolve possible problems or inquiries, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to private entities, law enforcement, or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate.  
back to FAQ

9\. What about the privacy of visitors who are 13 and under?   
If you are under the age of 13, you do not have permission to use our website. We do not knowingly collect, use, or disclose personally identifiably information about users who are under the age of 13. If you are the parent or guardian of a minor under 13 years of age and believe they have disclosed personally identifiable information to this website, please contact us at [company@SalesTeamAutomation.com](mailto:company@salesteamautomation.com) so that we may delete the minor's information.  
back to FAQ

10\. What are cookies and how do they collect, use, and distribute information?   
Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers and stores to your computer's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can make the web more useful by storing information about your preferences on a particular site, so that you do not have to reenter them each time you visit a site.  
We use cookies or IP addresses for a number of tasks, including helping us to tailor a website or a marketing message to better match your needs and interests and allowing us to better understand how visitors use our website. Sales Team Automation and its ad servers use cookies to assign your Internet browser a unique random number, a sort of anonymous user ID that is stored in a file on your computer. This unique identification number automatically identifies your browser - but not you - to our computers whenever you interact on our website. Our ad server collects your IP address, browser type, operating system, time and date a particular ad was served, and an advertisement tag used to call up an ad. We use a shopping cart cookie to indefinitely store and keep track of items you selected until you check out or delete the items.  
The use of cookies is an industry standard, and many major websites use them to provide useful features to their customers. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's computer. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You are always free to instruct your web browser to decline our cookies if it has the capability to do so, but some parts of our website may not work properly if you do so. For more general information on cookies, see [http://www.cookiecentral.com](http://www.cookiecentral.com/).  
In the future, we may place advertising on our website that originates from third-party advertisers and/or advertising agencies. Even though these advertisements will be displayed on our website, cookies may be assigned by the advertisers themselves. We do not control these cookies.  
back to FAQ

**11\. Where can I find any changes to the Privacy Policy?**  
This Policy was implemented on January 1, 2002 and is effective immediately. If you do not agree with the terms of this Policy, you should send us an e-mail opting out of it at [company@SalesTeamAutomation.com](mailto:company@salesteamautomation.com) and we will reluctantly cancel your account privileges and remove your data (subject to the limitations described above). If we make changes to any terms or conditions of the Policy, the changes will be incorporated into this document so you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and to whom we will disclose it. We may change, add, or remove portions of this Policy without prior notice to you at any time.  
back to FAQ

**Policy of Terminating Privileges For Infringement; Notice and Procedure for Making Claims of Copyright **Infringement** Infringement**

Pursuant to 17 U.S.C. § 512 as amended by Title II of the Digital Millennium Copyright Act, Sales Team Automation LLC, will terminate the account of any subscriber who uses his or her account privileges to unlawfully transmit copyrighted material without a license, valid defense or fair use privilege to do so. After proper notification by the copyright holder or its agent to Sales Team Automation and later confirmation through court order or an admission by the subscriber that an account has been an instrument of unlawful infringement, Sales Team Automation will terminate the infringing subscriber's account. Sales Team Automation may also in its sole discretion decide to terminate a subscriber's account privileges prior to that time if it has good faith belief that infringement has in fact occurred. In addition, pursuant to 17 U.S.C. § 512(c), Sales Team Automation has implemented procedures for receiving written notification of claimed infringements and for processing such claims in accordance with the Act. Sales Team Automation respects the intellectual property of others, and we ask our users to do the same. 

Any written notice describing the infringing activity must include the following information:  
1\. an electronic or physical signature of the person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed;   
2\. a description of the allegedly infringing work or material;   
3\. a description of where the allegedly infringing material is located on the site;   
4\. information reasonably sufficient to allow us to contact you, such as your address, telephone number, and email address;   
5\. a statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the disputed use of the material is not authorized by the copyright or other proprietary right owner, its agent, or the law; and   
6\. a statement by you that the above information in your notification is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that you are the copyright owner or authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed. 

**Sales Team Automation Website Terms of Service**

Welcome to the Sales Team Automation website. We hope you find it to be informative. Your use of this website is subject to the following terms and conditions, and your use of the website constitutes acceptance of these terms ("Agreement"). If you do not agree to the terms stated below OR DO NOT AGREE WITH THIS WEBSITE 'S PRIVACY POLICY, THEN YOU MUST immediately LEAVE this website, AS YOU DO NOT HAVE OUR PERMISSION TO USE IT.

**Use of Materials on Our Website**

**Software**

Sales Team Automation provides this website for information and education about our company products and services. You may view any of the pages within the site and, if you would like, download copies of software from our server ("Software") in accordance with our accompanying software license ("Software License Agreement"). An end user will be unable to install any Software that is accompanied by or includes a License Agreement, unless he or she first agrees to the License Agreement's terms and conditions. The Software is made available for downloading solely for use by end users according to the License Agreement. 

**Other Content**

Without the prior written permission of Sales Team Automation, you may not reproduce, distribute, modify, display, prepare derivative works based on, repost, or otherwise use the content of this website in a way inconsistent with its posted terms and conditions. You may not delete or change any copyright, trademark, or other proprietary notice. Except as expressly provided within these terms and conditions, nothing contained herein shall be construed as conferring any license or right under any copyright or other intellectual property right.  
**  
Notices and Procedures for Making Claims of Copyright Infringement**

Sales Team Automation respects the intellectual rights of others and expects that you will do the same. Sales Team Automation complies with the Digital millennium Copyright Act. Pursuant to Title 17, United States Code, Section 512(c)(2), notification of claimed copyright infringement must be sent to the Service Provider's Designated Agent. Click here to see Sales Team Automation's "Policy of Terminating Privileges For Infringement, Notice and Procedure for Making Claims of Copyright Infringement." 

**Trademark Information**

The following marks used on this website are the proprietary trademarks of Sales Team Automation Inc.: Sales Team Automation, Sales Team Automation (stylized-handwritten logo), are registered trademarks of Sales Team Automation LLC in the United States and/or other countries. These trademarks or any confusingly similar marks may not be used in any way that would constitute trademark infringement.

The names of other companies and products mentioned on this site may be the trademarks of their respective owners. No sponsorship, endorsement, or affiliation with any other company, product, person, or event is intended or should be inferred. The following trademarks used on this website are trademarks of entities identified below, and are used either with permission or for identification purposes only: 

1\. All other trademarks mentioned are property of their respective owners.   
Any rights not expressly granted herein are reserved. 

**User Submissions**

Sales Team Automation likes to hear from you. However, please keep in mind that unless a prior agreement exists between Sales Team Automation and you, any material, information, or other communication you send to or post on this site ("Communications") will be considered non-confidential and nonproprietary. Sales Team Automation will have no obligations to you with respect to the Communications and will feel free to copy, disclose, distribute, incorporate, and otherwise use the Communications for any and all purposes, including design development, manufacturing, and marketing of any Sales Team Automation products and/or services using this Communication.

Prohibition Against Obscene, Pornographic, Libelous, or Harassing Submissions

Users are prohibited from posting or transmitting to or from this website any unlawful, harassing, threatening, libelous, defamatory, obscene, pornographic, or other materials that violate any law of the United States, the State of Utah, or the state or nation from which you accessed this site. VIOLATION OF THIS TERM WILL RESULT IN IMMEDIATE TERMINATION OF ANY REGISTERED USER'S PRIVILEGES, AS WELL AS NOTIFICATION TO THE APPROPRIATE AUTHORITIES, IF APPLICABLE.

Use of Personally Identifiable Information

Any and all information submitted to or gathered at this website is governed by the Sales Team Automation privacy policy.

**Disclaimer of Warranties and Limitation of Liability**

The materials on this website are provided "as is" without any implied warranty of any kind, including warranties of merchantability, noninfringement of intellectual property, fitness for a particular purpose, informational content, or system integration. Sales Team Automation expressly disclaims any warranty, whether express or perceived, created by any public statement made regarding this website or Sales Team Automation's products or services, including without limitation, as a result of Sales Team Automation's public statements or advertising. In no event shall Sales Team Automation or its suppliers or agents be liable for any damages whatsoever due to your use or inability to use this website (including, without limitation, damages for loss of profits, business interruption, or loss of information), even if Sales Team Automation has been advised of the possibility of such damages. Because some jurisdictions prohibit the exclusion or limitation of liability for consequential or incidental damages, the above limitation may not apply to you.

**User Chat Rooms, Bulletin Boards  
**  
Sales Team Automation may, but is not obligated to, monitor or review any submissions or postings where users transmit or post Communications or communicate solely with each other on our website in chat rooms, bulletin boards, or other user forums. Sales Team Automation, however, will have no liability relating to the content of user Communications, either for the content itself or relating to any screening or failure to screen such content, whether or not arising under the laws of copyright, libel, privacy, or otherwise. (Please see "Policy Against Obscene, Pornographic, Libelous or Harassing Summissions," "Notices and Procedures for Making Claims of Copyright Infringement," and "Privacy Policy.") 

**Links to Other Websites or Materials  
**  
For your convenience and information, this website links to certain other websites that we feel may be of interest to our visitors. The links in this area will allow you to leave the Sales Team Automation website. Please be aware that these linked-to sites are not under the control of Sales Team Automation. We are not responsible for either the content or the privacy policy of any linked site or any link contained in a linked site. Sales Team Automation reserves the right to terminate any link or linking program at any time. Unless otherwise specified, Sales Team Automation does not endorse companies or products to which it links, and reserves the right to note as such on its web pages. If you decide to access any of the third-party sites linked to this site, you do so entirely at your own risk.

**Applicable Laws/Choice of Form**

This site is sponsored by Sales Team Automation LLC from its offices in Springville, Ut. Sales Team Automation makes no representation that the materials in the site are appropriate for use in other locations, and access to them from territories where their content is illegal is prohibited. Those who choose to access this site from other locations do so on their own initiative, and are responsible for compliance with local laws. You may not use or export anything within this website in violation of U.S. export laws and regulations. Any claim relating to this website or its contents shall be governed by the laws of the State of Utah, without regard to Utah law regarding choice of law. Any legal action to enforce or obtain an interpretation of this privacy policy must be filed in the Fourth Judicial District Court of Utah County, the Third Judicial District Court of Salt Lake County or the Federal Courts in the State of Utah.

**Change of Terms**

Sales Team Automation may change or revise this Agreement at any time by updating this posting. Upon posting, any such new terms and conditions will become immediately effective, unless otherwise stated. We encourage you to visit this page from time to time to review the current terms and conditions because they are binding upon you.

Copyright © 2004 Sales Team Automation LLC, All rights reserved. Sales Team Automation (stylized-handwritten logo), are trademarks of Sales Team Automation LLC, in the USA and other countries. All other registered trademarks, third-party brands and names are the property of their respective owners.
